Glove Cities Area Joint Board, ACTWU; Records apap017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Records1933-1989
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Records
apap017
5 cubic ft.
The Glove Cities Area Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) was founded in Gloversville, N.Y., 1954. This Joint Board originally had jurisdiction over the clothing workers unions in Gloversville and Johnstown, N.Y., and nearby villages. These locals were primarily locals of glove and leather goods workers.
Access
Access to these records is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were lent to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by the Glove Cities Area Joint Board, ACTWU, and were subsequently microfilmed as a part of the Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., Labor History Project. The originals have been returned to the Glove Cities Area Joint Board.
Biographical History
The Glove Cities Area Joint Board of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) was founded in Gloversville, N.Y., 1954. This Joint Board originally had jurisdiction over the clothing workers unions in Gloversville and Johnstown, N.Y., and nearby villages. These locals were primarily locals of glove and leather goods workers.
The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Collar and Pajama Workers of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) was founded in Troy, N.Y., in 1934 with jurisdiction over locals of Clothing Workers in Albany, Schenectady, and Rensselaer counties. In 1978, both joint boards were affected by the merger of ACWA with the Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), which produced the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). In 1983 the joint boards merged into one, keeping the title Glove Cities Area Joint Board. These records are particularly important for the information contained an labor strife in Fulton County, N.Y., from the 1930's to the 1950"s. For related records, see the records of the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board, ACTWU.
Scope and Contents
Contains the records of the Glove Cities Area Joint Board, including minutes, 1954-87; and subject files, 1978-84. Also contains the records of the Capitol District Joint Board: minutes, 1966-70, 1972; minutes of the Capitol District Joint Board Realty Corporation, 1952-53, 1981-83; minutes of the House Committee, 1957-59; subject file, 1950-79; photographs, 1950's-60's; and membership card file, 1936-83. Also contains the records of Glove Cities' locals: Local 292, Gloversville Cutters and Layers Off, minutes, 1939-46, 1950-54, 1958-71; Local 743, Knit Woolen Workers, minutes, 1958-67; Local 1712, Tannery and Leather Workers, minutes, 1950-55, 1960-84, 1987; Local 1714, Consolidated Glove Cutters and Shavers, minutes, 1942-65, 1970-74; and Local 1715, Operators and Day Hands, minutes, 1969-81. Also contains the records of the locals of the Capitol District Joint Board: Local 7JTU, minutes, 1973-75; Local 163, Shirt, Collar and Uniform Workers, minutes, 1982-83; Local 314, Shirt, Bleachery and Neckwear Workers, minutes, 1942-54, 1958, 1960-70; and Local 429, minutes, 1945, 1957-48, 1950-55, 1959-71, 1975. The records of the Capital District Joint Board also contain minutes of the Troy Area Labor Council, 1981-82; and the Capital District Union Label & Service Trades Council, general files with many photographs, 1960-80.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: Series 1- The Glove Cities Area Joint Board 1937-1987, Subseries 1- Minutes of Joint Board Meetings 1954-1987, Subseries 2- Minutes of Locals' Meetings 1939-1987, Subseries 3- Subject Files 1941-1986, Series 2- The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Collar and Pajama Workers 1933- 1989, Subseries 1- Subject Files 1950- 1985, Subseries 2- Locals Files 1933- 1989, Subseries 3- Capitol District Union Label and Service Trades Council 1960- 1981, Subseries 4- Membership Card Files 1933-1983, Subseries 5- Photographs 1955- 1975.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Schenectady, New York; Rensselaer County, New York; Labor; Albany, New York; New York (State); Reports; Proposals; The Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union
- The Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1954-1987; 1
  - Minutes of Joint Board Meetings, 1954-1987; 1.1; 0.33 cubic ft.
    Arrangement
    Arranged Chronologically.
    - Minutes, 1954-1957 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1962-1964 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1965-1968 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Locals' Meetings, 1939-1987; 1.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    Arranged Chronologically by Local.
    - Local 292, 1939-1942 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 12)
    - Local 292, 1943-1946; 1950-1954 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 13)
    - Local 292, 1958-1969 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 14)
    - Local 432, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 15)
    - Local 743, 1958-1962 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 16)
    - Local 743, 1963-1967 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 17)
    - Local 1712, 1950-1951; 1955 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 18)
    - Local 1712, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 19)
    - Local 1712, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 20)
    - Local 1712, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 21)
    - Local 1712, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 22)
    - Local 1712, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 23)
    - Local 1712, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 24)
    - Local 1712, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 25)
    - Local 1712, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 26)
    - Local 1712, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 27)
    - Local 1712, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 28)
    - Local 1712, 1984 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 29)
    - Local 1712, 1987 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 30)
    - Consoilidated Cutters and Shavers Union (became Local 1714), 1942-1954 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 31)
    - Local 1714, 1954-1957 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 32)
    - Local 1714, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 33)
    - Local 1714, 1960-1961 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 34)
    - Local 1714, 1954-1957 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 35)
    - Local 1714, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 36)
    - Local 1714, 1960-1962 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 37)
    - Local 1714, 1963-1965 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 38)
    - Local 1714, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 39)
    - Local 1715, 1971- 1974 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 40)
    - Local 1715, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 41)
    - Local 1715, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 42)
    - Local 1715, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 43)
  - Subject Files, 1941-1986; 1.3; 1 cubic ft.
    Arranged Alphabetically.
    - American Coat, Apron Supply and Laundry, Inc. (Local 432), Contracts, 1966; 1971 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 1)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1981-1984 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 2)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 February (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 3)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 March (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 4)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 May (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 5)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 May (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 6)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 June (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 7)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 July (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 8)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 August (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 9)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 September (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 10)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 November (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 11)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1983 December (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 12)
    - Carville Leather and National Leather, 1984 January (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 13)
    - Cayadutta Tanning Company, Inc. (Local 1712), Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 14)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, ca. 1965; ca. 1985 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 15)
    - Glove Cutters Organizing Campaign, 1953 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 16)
    - Gloversville Knitting Co. (Layers-Off and Glove Workers Union Local 292), Contract, 1946 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 17)
    - Karg Brothers, Inc. (Local 1712), Contracts and Correspondence, 1951-1952; 1961 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 18)
    - Kilmer & Sons, Inc. (See R. L. Kilmer & Sons, Inc.), Undated (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 19)
    - Laundry and Cleaning Workers Union, Local 432, Correspondence, 1949-1957 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 20)
    - Layers-off and Glove Workers Union of Fulton County and Vicinity, Local 292, Charter, 1941 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 21)
    - Layers-off and Glove Workers Union of Fulton County and Vicinity, Local 292, Correspondence, 1944-1956 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 22)
    - Liberty Employees Association--Affiliation with Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 23)
    - Liberty Leather Corporation, Inc. (Local 1712), Contract, 1977 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 24)
    - Milligan & Higgins, Inc., Division of Hudson Industries, (Local 1712), Arbitration, 1976-1981 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 25)
    - Milligan & Higgins, Inc., Division of Hudson Industries, (Local 1712), Contracts, 1981; 1983 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 26)
    - Newsletter of Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 27)
    - NuFam, Inc., and Compo Industries, Inc. (Local 1712), Contracts, 1976-1978 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 28)
    - Operators and Day Hands Union, Local 1715, Charter, 1969 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 29)
    - Operators and Day Hands Union, Local 1715, Constitution and By-Laws, ca. 1975 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 30)
    - Photographs of Locals' Officers, 1953 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 31)
    - RAP Tanning Company, Inc. (Local 1712), Contract, 1977 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 32)
    - R. L. Kilmer & Sons, Inc. (Local 1714), Contracts, 1977-1982 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 33)
    - Service Linen Supply Co. (Local 432), Contracts, 1971-1986 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 34)
    - Tannery and Leather Workers Union, Local 2314, Charter, 1982 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 35)
    - Tannery and Leather workers Union, Local 2356, Charter, 1984 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 36)
    - United Tannery & Leather Workers Union, Local 1712, Constitution and and By-Laws, ca. 1975 (Box 2 (1-The Glove Cities Area Joint Board), Folder 37)
- The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Collar and Pajama Workers, 1950-1985; 2
  - Subject Files1, 1950-1985; 2.1; 0.33 cubic ft.
    Arranged Alphabetically
    - Arbitration with Cluett Peabody, 1969 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 1)
    - Cluett Peabody--Contracts, 1953 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 2)
    - Consolidation with the Glove Cities Area Joint Board, 1983 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 3)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, ca. 1960 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 5)
    - Kay's Caps Contract, 1979 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 6)
    - Minutes of Capitol District Joint Board Meetings, 1960 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 7)
    - Minutes of Capitol District Joint Board House Committee Meetings, 1955-1959 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 8)
    - Minutes of Capitol District Joint Board Realty Corporation, 1951-1953 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 9)
  - Locals Files, 1933-1989; 2.2; 0.67 cubic ft.
    Arranged by Chronologically by Local.
    - Local 7JTU Charter, 1936 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 1)
    - Local 7JTU Contracts, 1977 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 2)
    - Local 7JTU Minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 3)
    - Local 71 Minutes, 1936 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 4)
    - Local 163 Charter, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 5)
    - Local 185 Charter, 1934 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 6)
    - Local 196 charter, 1933 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 7)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1942-1946 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 8)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1947-1951 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 9)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1952-1958 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 10)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1960-1964 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 11)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1965-1969 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 12)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1970 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 13)
    - Local 314 Minutes, 1945-1953 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 14)
    - Local 384 Charter, 1941 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 15)
    - Local 429 Arbitration, 1988 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 16)
    - Local 429 Correspondence, 1960-1989 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 17)
    - Local 429 Minutes, 1945 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 18)
    - Local 429 Minutes, 1959-1973 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 19)
    - Local 429 Minutes, 1979-1989 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 20)
    - Local 429 Newspaper Clippings, 1986 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 21)
    - Local 429 Silver Anniversary Party--Program, 1968 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 22)
    - Local 429 Union booklet, ca. 1945 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 23)
    - Local 492 Charter, 1946 (Box 3 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 24)
  - Capitol District Union Label and Service Trades Council, 1965-1981; 2.3; 0.10 cubic ft.
    - Award of Merit Dinners, 1965; 1971-1981 (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 2)
  - Membership Card Files, Undated; 2.4; 0.67 cubic ft.
    - Files, A, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 3)
    - Files, B, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 4)
    - Files, C, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 5)
    - Files, D, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 6)
    - Files, E, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 7)
    - Files, F, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 8)
    - Files, G, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 9)
    - Files, H, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 10)
    - Files, I, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 11)
    - Files, J, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 12)
    - Files, K, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 13)
    - Files, L, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 14)
    - Files, M, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 15)
    - Files, N, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 16)
    - Files, 0, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 17)
    - Files, P, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 18)
    - Files, Q, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 19)
    - Files, R, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 20)
    - Files, S, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 21)
    - Files, T, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 22)
    - Files, U, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 23)
    - Files, V, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 24)
    - Files, W, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 25)
    - Files, Y, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 26)
    - Files, Z, Undated (Box 4 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Folder 27)
  - Photographs, 1960-1981; 2.5; 0.67 cubic ft.
    - Charter Presentation--Photographs, 1960 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 1)
    - Cotrell & Leonard Sympathy Picketing--Photographs, ca. 1967 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 2)
    - Farah Sympathy Picketing--Photographs, 1974 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 3)
    - Union Label Banquet and proclamation signing--Photographs, 1960 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 4)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1961 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 5)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1962 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 6)
    - Union Label Banquet and proclamation signing--Photographs, 1963 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 7)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1964 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 8)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1966 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 9)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1973 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 10)
    - Union Label Banquet--Photographs, 1975 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 11)
    - Union Label Convention--Labor Management Show--Photograph, 1960 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 12)
    - Union Label Queen--Photographs, ca. 1960 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 13)
    - Union Label Week--Photographs, 1962 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 14)
    - Union Label Week Proclamation--Photographs, 1961 (Box 5 (2-The Capitol District Joint Board of the Shirt, Col), Item 15)